<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Millennial</title>
        <description>a minimalist Jekyll theme for running a blog or publication</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 09:00:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 09:00:43 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v4.3.3</generator>
        
            <item>
                <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR&lt;/code&gt; is a four-digit number, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MONTH&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DAY&lt;/code&gt; are both two-digit numbers, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MARKUP&lt;/code&gt; is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Tom&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &apos;Hi, Tom&apos; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 08:44:01 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-jekyll</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-jekyll</guid>
                
                
                <category>jekyll</category>
                
                <category>update</category>
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Graphic Designer On The Road</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A graphic designer is a professional within the graphic design and graphic arts industry who assembles together images, typography, or motion graphics to create a piece of design. A graphic designer creates the graphics primarily for published, printed or electronic media, such as brochures (sometimes) and advertising. They are also sometimes responsible for typesetting, illustration, user interfaces, web design, or take a teaching position. A core responsibility of the designer’s job is to present information in a way that is both accessible and memorable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A degree or certificate from an accredited trade school is usually considered essential for a graphic design position. After a career history has been established, though, the graphic designer’s experience and number of years in the business are considered the primary qualifications. A portfolio, which is the primary method for demonstrating these qualifications, is usually required to be shown at job interviews, and is constantly developed throughout a designer’s career. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Graphic_designer&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ice molecules can exhibit up to sixteen different phases &lt;em&gt;(packing geometries)&lt;/em&gt; that depend on temperature and pressure. When water is cooled rapidly (quenching), up to three different types of amorphous ice can form depending on the history of its pressure and temperature. When cooled slowly correlated proton tunneling occurs below 20 K giving rise to macroscopic quantum phenomena. Virtually all the ice on Earth’s surface and in its atmosphere is of a hexagonal crystalline structure denoted as ice Ih (spoken as “ice one h”) with minute traces of cubic ice denoted as ice Ic. The most common phase transition to ice Ih occurs when liquid water is cooled below 0°C (273.15K, 32°F) at standard atmospheric pressure. It may also be deposited directly by water vapor, as happens in the formation of frost. The transition from ice to water is melting and from ice directly to water vapor is sublimation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;characteristics&quot;&gt;Characteristics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a naturally-occurring crystalline inorganic solid with an ordered structure, ice is considered a mineral.[citation needed] It possesses a regular crystalline structure based on the molecule of water, which consists of a single oxygen atom covalently bonded to two hydrogen atoms, or H-O-H. However, many of the physical properties of water and ice are controlled by the formation of hydrogen bonds between adjacent oxygen and hydrogen atoms; while it is a weak bond, it is nonetheless critical in controlling the structure of both water and ice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ice contains no future , just the past, sealed away. As if they’re alive, everything in the world is sealed up inside, clear and distinct. Ice can preserve all kinds of things that way- cleanly, clearly. That’s the essence of ice, the role it plays.”
&lt;cite&gt;― Haruki Murakami&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An unusual property of ice frozen at atmospheric pressure is that the solid is approximately 8.3% less dense than liquid water. The density of ice is 0.9167 g/cm3 at 0 °C,[4] whereas water has a density of 0.9998 g/cm³ at the same temperature. Liquid water is densest, essentially 1.00 g/cm³, at 4 °C and becomes less dense as the water molecules begin to form the hexagonal crystals[5] of ice as the freezing point is reached. This is due to hydrogen bonding dominating the intermolecular forces, which results in a packing of molecules less compact in the solid. Density of ice increases slightly with decreasing temperature and has a value of 0.9340 g/cm³ at −180 °C (93 K).[6]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When water freezes, it increases in volume (about 9% for freshwater).[7] The effect of expansion during freezing can be dramatic, and ice expansion is a basic cause of freeze-thaw weathering of rock in nature and damage to building foundations and roadways from frost heaving. It is also a common cause of the flooding of houses when water pipes burst due to the pressure of expanding water when it freezes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result of this process is that ice &lt;em&gt;(in its most common form)&lt;/em&gt; floats on liquid water, which is an important feature in Earth’s biosphere. It has been argued that without this property, natural bodies of water would freeze, in some cases permanently, from the bottom up,[8] resulting in a loss of bottom-dependent animal and plant life in fresh and sea water. Sufficiently thin ice sheets allow light to pass through while protecting the underside from short-term weather extremes such as wind chill. This creates a sheltered environment for bacterial and algal colonies. When sea water freezes, the ice is riddled with brine-filled channels which sustain sympagic organisms such as bacteria, algae, copepods and annelids, which in turn provide food for animals such as krill and specialised fish like the bald notothen, fed upon in turn by larger animals such as emperor penguins and minke whales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When ice melts, it absorbs as much energy as it would take to heat an equivalent mass of water by 80 °C. During the melting process, the temperature remains constant at 0 °C. While melting, any energy added breaks the hydrogen bonds between ice (water) molecules. Energy becomes available to increase the thermal energy (temperature) only after enough hydrogen bonds are broken that the ice can be considered liquid water. The amount of energy consumed in breaking hydrogen bonds in the transition from ice to water is known as the heat of fusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with water, ice absorbs light at the red end of the spectrum preferentially as the result of an overtone of an oxygen-hydrogen (O-H) bond stretch. Compared with water, this absorption is shifted toward slightly lower energies. Thus, ice appears blue, with a slightly greener tint than for liquid water. Since absorption is cumulative, the color effect intensifies with increasing thickness or if internal reflections cause the light to take a longer path through the ice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Graphic-Designer-On-The-Road</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Review: A Week With the Apple Watch</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/strong&gt; is a smartwatch developed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/&quot;&gt;Apple Inc&lt;/a&gt;. It incorporates fitness tracking and health-oriented capabilities as well as integration with iOS and other Apple products and services. The device is available in four variants: Apple Watch Sport, Apple Watch, Apple Watch Hermès, and Apple Watch Edition. The Watch is distinguished by different combinations of cases and first or third party interchangeable bands. Apple Watch relies on a wirelessly connected iPhone to perform many of its default functions such as calling and texting. It is compatible with the iPhone 5 or later models running iOS 8.2 or later, through the use of Bluetooth or Wi-Fi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Announced by Tim Cook on September 9, 2014, the device was available for pre-order on April 10 and began shipping on April 24, 2015. The Apple Watch quickly became the best-selling wearable device, with the shipment of 4.2 million smartwatches in the second quarter of 2015, according to analyst firm Canalys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“You can only do so many things great, and you should cast aside everything else.”
&lt;cite&gt;― Tim Cook&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rumors surrounded an Apple-developed wearable back as far as 2011, which conceptualized the device as a variation of the iPod that would curve around the user’s wrist, and feature Siri integration. On February 10, 2013, both The New York Times and The Wall Street Journal reported that Apple was beginning to develop an iOS-based smartwatch with a curved display. On February 12, 2013, Bloomberg reported that Apple’s smartwatch project was “beyond the experimentation phase in its development”, and had a team of at least 100 designers were working on the project. Further reports in March 2013 indicated that Apple planned to release the device by the end of the year. In July 2013, Financial Times reported that Apple had begun hiring more employees to work on the smartwatch, and that it was targeting a possible retail release in late 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;unveiling--release&quot;&gt;Unveiling &amp;amp; Release&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In April 2014, Apple CEO &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tim_Cook&quot;&gt;Tim Cook&lt;/a&gt; told The Wall Street Journal that the company was planning to launch new product categories that year, but did not reveal any specifics. In June 2014, Reuters reported that production was expected to begin in July for a release in October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Watch was first unveiled after a classic and ever infamous &lt;em&gt;“We do have ‘one more thing’…”&lt;/em&gt; slide, which heard enormous applause, on September 9, 2014 during a press event which also saw the introduction of the iPhone 6. After the reveal video, the auditorium erupted with applause while Tim Cook rolled back his sleeve, revealing an Apple Watch on his wrist. Speaking about the device, Apple CEO Tim Cook explained that Apple Watch was “a new, intimate way to communicate from your wrist, and a comprehensive health and fitness device.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In comparison to other Apple products and competing smartwatches, marketing of Apple Watch focused more on advertising the device as a fashion accessory; a 12-page advertising spread for Apple Watch in an issue of Vogue focused primarily on the different body and band styles available, and downplayed the technological aspects of it. Apple has also, in particular, focused upon its health and fitness-oriented features, competing against dedicated activity trackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;image-card width-full caption&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/apple-watch-in-car.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Apple Watch&quot; /&gt;
  
  &lt;figcaption class=&quot;caption-text&quot;&gt;Apple watch on the wrist&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;release&quot;&gt;Release&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre-orders for Apple Watch began on April 10, 2015, with an official release on April 24.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On launch, Apple Watch was not available at Apple Store; beginning on April 10, 2015, customers could receive appointments for demonstrations and fitting, but the device was not in-stock for walk-in purchase, and had to be reserved and ordered online (however, sales representatives are able to assist in the process). CNET felt that this distribution model was designed to prevent Apple Store locations from having long line-ups due to high demand. Selected Apple Watch models were available in-store at certain luxury boutiques and authorized Apple resellers in limited quantities. On June 4, 2015, Apple announced that it did plan to stock Apple Watch models at its retail locations. On August 24, 2015 during an earnings call, Best Buy announced that it would begin stocking Apple Watch at its retail stores by the end of September. Both T-Mobile US and Sprint also announced plans to offer Apple Watch through its retail stores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Design is a funny word. Some people think design means how it looks. But of course, if you dig deeper, it’s really how it works.” &lt;cite&gt;― Steve Jobs&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 9, 2015, in Apple’s Special Event, Apple launched a new collection of Apple Watch in a collaboration with Hermès. This new collection of Apple Watch is named as Apple Watch Hermès, comes in stainless steel body with finely crafted leather bands in distinctive styles from Hermès, including the Single Tour, Double Tour and Cuff models. Apple Watch Hermès is available only in selected retail stores of Apple and Hermès.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The device was not branded as “iWatch” (which would put it in line with its other product lines) due to trademark conflicts in certain territories; in the United States, the iWatch trademark is owned by OMG Electronics—who was crowdfunding a device under the same name, and is owned in the European Union by Irish firm Probendi. In July 2015, Probendi sued Apple Inc. for trademark infringement, arguing that through keyword advertising on the Google search engine, it caused advertising for the Apple Watch to appear on search results pages when users searched for the trademarked term “iWatch”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Watch finally goes on sale in India on Nov. 6. The device also has launched in Chile, the Philippines, and South Africa.  [ &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_Watch&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/a-week-with-the-apple-watch</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-week-with-the-apple-watch</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Basic Rules For Walking In The Mountains</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;em&gt;United States, Canada, the Republic of Ireland, and United Kingdom,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;hiking&lt;/strong&gt; refers to walking outdoors on a trail, or off trail, for recreational purposes. A day hike refers to a hike that can be completed in a single day. However, in the United Kingdom, the word walking is also used, as well as rambling, while walking in mountainous areas is called hillwalking. In Northern England, Including the Lake District and Yorkshire Dales, fellwalking describes hill or mountain walks, as fell is the common word for both features there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hiking can sometimes involves bushwhacking and hiking is sometimes referred to as such. This specifically refers to difficult walking through dense forest, undergrowth, or bushes, where forward progress requires pushing vegetation aside. In extreme cases of bushwhacking, where the vegetation is so dense that human passage is impeded, a machete is used to clear a pathway. The Australian term bushwalking refers to both on and off-trail hiking. Common terms for hiking used by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Zealand&quot;&gt;New Zealanders&lt;/a&gt; are tramping (particularly for overnight and longer trips), walking or bushwalking. Trekking is the preferred word used to describe multi-day hiking in the mountainous regions of India, Pakistan, Nepal, North America, South America, Iran and in the highlands of East Africa. Hiking a long-distance trail from end-to-end is also referred to as trekking and as thru-hiking in some places. In North America, multi-day hikes, usually with camping, are referred to as &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Backpacking_(wilderness)&quot;&gt;backpacking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;long-distance-hiking&quot;&gt;Long Distance Hiking&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frequently nowadays long distance hikes (walking tours) are undertaken along long distance paths, including the National Trails in England and Wales, the National Trail System in the USA and The Grande Randonnée (France), Grote Routepaden, or Lange-afstand-wandelpaden (Holland), Grande Rota (Portugal), Gran Recorrido (Spain) is a network of long-distance footpaths in Europe, mostly in France, Belgium, the Netherlands and Spain. There are extensive networks in other European countries of long distance trails, as well as in Canada, Australia, New Zealand, Nepal, and to a lesser extent other Asiatic countries, like Turkey, Israel, and Jordan. In the Alps of Austria, Slovenia, Switzerland, Germany, France, and Italy walking tours are often made from ‘hut-to-hut’, using an extensive system of mountain huts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;image-card width-full caption&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/mountain-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mountain&quot; /&gt;
  
  &lt;figcaption class=&quot;caption-text&quot;&gt;Norway is Beautiful&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the late 20th-century there has been a proliferation of official and unofficial long distance routes, which mean that hikers now are more likely to refer to using a long distance way (Britain), trail (USA), The Grande Randonnée (France), etc., than setting out on a walking tour. Early examples of long distance paths, include the Appalachian Trail in the USA and the Pennine Way in Britain. Pilgrimage routes are now treated, by some walkers, as long distance routes, and the route taken by the British National Trail the North Downs Way closely follows that of the Pilgrims’ Way to Canterbury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hiking times can be estimated by Naismith’s rule or Tobler’s hiking function.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;equipment&quot;&gt;Equipment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The equipment required for hiking depends on the length of the hike, but day hikers generally carry at least water, food, a map, and rain-proof gear. Hikers usually wear sturdy hiking boots for mountain walking and backpacking, as protection from the rough terrain, as well as providing increased stability. The Mountaineers club recommends a list of “Ten Essentials” equipment for hiking, including a compass, sunglasses, sunscreen, a flashlight, a first aid kit, a fire starter, and a knife. Other groups recommend items such as hat, gloves, insect repellent, and an emergency blanket. A GPS navigation device can also be helpful and route cards may be used as a guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Returning home is the most difficult part of long-distance hiking; You have grown outside the puzzle and your piece no longer fits.”
&lt;cite&gt;― Cindy Ross&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proponents of ultralight backpacking argue that long lists of required items for multi-day hikes increases pack weight, and hence fatigue and the chance of injury. Instead, they recommend reducing pack weight, in order to make hiking long distances easier. Even the use of hiking boots on long-distances hikes is controversial among ultralight hikers, because of their weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;environmental-impact&quot;&gt;Environmental Impact&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Natural environments are often fragile, and may be accidentally damaged, especially when a large number of hikers are involved. For example, years of gathering wood can strip an alpine area of valuable nutrients. and some species, such as martens or bighorn sheep, are very sensitive to the presence of humans, especially around mating season. Generally, protected areas such as parks have regulations in place to protect the environment, so as to minimize such impact. Such regulations include banning wood fires, restricting camping to established camp sites, disposing or packing out faecal matter, and imposing a quota on the number of hikers. Many hikers espouse the philosophy of Leave No Trace, following strict practices on dealing with food waste, food packaging, and other impact on the environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Human waste is often a major source of environmental impact from hiking, and can contaminate the watershed and make other hikers ill. ‘Catholes’ dug 10 to 25 cm (4 to 10 inches) deep, depending on local soil composition and covered after use, at least 60 m (200 feet) away from water sources and trails, are recommended to reduce the risk of bacterial contamination. [ &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hiking&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/basic-rules-for-walking-in-the-mountains</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/basic-rules-for-walking-in-the-mountains</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>How to Set Up Your New iPhone 6 the Right Way</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;iPhone 6&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;iPhone 6 Plus&lt;/strong&gt; are &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smartphone&quot;&gt;smartphones&lt;/a&gt; designed and marketed by Apple Inc. The devices are part of the iPhone series and were unveiled on September 9, 2014, and released on September 19, 2014. The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus jointly serve as successors to the iPhone 5C and iPhone 5S.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus include a number of changes over their predecessor, including models with larger 4.7 and 5.5 inches (120 and 140 mm) displays, a faster processor, upgraded cameras, improved LTE and Wi-Fi connectivity and support for a near field communications-based mobile payments offering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre-orders of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus exceeded four million within its first 24 hours of availability—an Apple record. More than ten million iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus devices were sold in the first three days, another Apple record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 9, 2015, the 128 GB version of both the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus was discontinued along with the gold version of both phones, but the 16 GB and 64 GB versions of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus in silver and space gray remain available for sale at a reduced price due to the release of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_6S&quot;&gt;iPhone 6S and iPhone 6S Plus flagship devices&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history&quot;&gt;History&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Centered around the device’s size; the majority of iPhone models have used 3.5-inch displays—which are smaller than screens used by flagship phones from competitors. The last change in size for the iPhone series came with the iPhone 5; the phone and its immediate successors featured a display that was taller, but the same width as prior models, measuring at 4 inches diagonally. Following Apple’s loss in smartphone market share to companies producing phones with larger displays reports as early as January 2014 suggested that Apple was preparing to launch new iPhone models with larger, 4.7-inch and 5.5-inch displays. Reports prior to its unveiling also speculated the possibility that Apple would use a new iPhone model to introduce a mobile payments platform using near-field communications—a technology that has been incorporated into many Android phones, but has experienced a low adoption rate among users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What we want to do is make a leapfrog product that is way smarter than any mobile device has ever been, and super-easy to use. This is what iPhone is. OK? So, we’re going to reinvent the phone. &lt;cite&gt;- Steve Jobs, 2007.&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus were officially unveiled during a press event at the Flint Center for Performing Arts in Cupertino, California on September 9, 2014. The event featured other previously-rumored product announcements by Apple alongside the new iPhone models, including the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_Pay&quot;&gt;Apple Pay&lt;/a&gt; mobile payment platform, and the company’s entry into the wearable computing market with the Apple Watch smart watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;image-card width-full caption&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/iphone-in-hand.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Apple&quot; /&gt;
  
  &lt;figcaption class=&quot;caption-text&quot;&gt;iPhone 6&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus were unveiled on September 9, 2014 and released on September 19, 2014; pre-orders began on September 12, 2014, with the iPhone 6 starting at US$649 and the iPhone 6 Plus starting at US$749. In China, where the iPhone 5S and 5C were the first models in the iPhone series to be released in the country on the same day as their international launch, Apple notified local wireless carriers that it would be unable to release the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus in China on the 19th because there were “details which are not ready”; local media reported that the devices had not yet been approved by the Ministry of Industry and Information Technology, and earlier in the year, a news report by state broadcaster China Central Television alleged that iPhone devices were a threat to national security because iOS 7’s “frequent locations” function could expose “state secrets.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On August 2015 Apple admitted that some iPhone 6 Plus may have faulty cameras that could be causing photos to look blurry and initiated a replacement program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On September 9, 2015 the 128 GB version of both the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus was discontinued along with the gold version of both phones, the 16 GB and 64 GB versions of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus in silver and space gray remain available for sale at a reduced price due to the release of the iPhone 6S and iPhone 6S Plus flagship devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;specifications&quot;&gt;Specifications&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The design of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are influenced by that of the iPad Air with a glass front that is curved around the edges of the display, and an aluminum rear that contains two plastic strips for the antenna. Both models come in gold, silver, and “space gray” finishes. The iPhone 6 has a thickness of 6.9 millimetres (0.27 in), while the iPhone 6 Plus is 7.1 mm (0.28 in) in thickness; both are thinner than the iPhone 5S and iPhone 5C, with the iPhone 6 being Apple’s thinnest phone to date. The most significant changes to the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are its displays; both branded as “Retina HD Display” and “ion-strengthened”, the iPhone 6 display is 4.7 inches in size with a 16:9 resolution of 1334x750 (326 PPI, minus one row of pixels), while the iPhone 6 Plus includes a 5.5-inch 1920x1080 (1080p) display (401 PPI). The displays use a multiple-domain LCD panel, dubbed “dual-domain pixels”; the RGB pixels themselves are skewed in pattern, so that every pixel is seen from a different angle. This technique helps improve the viewing angles of the display.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To accommodate the larger physical size of the iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus, the power button was moved to the side of the phone instead of the top to improve its accessibility. The iPhone 6 features a 6.91 Wh (1810 mAh) battery, while the iPhone 6 Plus features a 11.1 Wh (2915 mAh) battery. Unlike the previous model, the rear-facing camera is not flush with the rear of the device, and has a slight “bulge” around the lens. It has a dual-core 1.4 GHz Cyclone processor (ARM v8-based). [ &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_6&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt; ]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/set-up-your-new-iphone-6-the-Right-Way</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/set-up-your-new-iphone-6-the-Right-Way</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>design</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>The Advantages &amp; Disadvantages of Working from Home</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;A work at home parent is an entrepreneur who works from home and integrates parenting into his or her business activities. They are sometimes referred to as a WAHM &lt;em&gt;(work at home mom)&lt;/em&gt; or a WAHD &lt;em&gt;(work at home dad)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entrepreneurs choose to run businesses from home for a variety of reasons, including lower business expenses, personal health limitations, eliminating commuting, or in order to have a more flexible schedule. This flexibility can give an entrepreneur more options when planning tasks, business and non-business, including parenting duties. While some home-based entrepreneurs opt for childcare outside the home,[1] others integrate child rearing into their work day and workspace. The latter are considered work-at-home parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many WAHPs start home-based businesses in order to care for their children while still creating income. The desire to care for one’s own children, the incompatibility of a 9-to-5 work day with school hours or sick days, and the expense of childcare prompt many parents to change or leave their jobs in the workforce to be available to their children. Many WAHPs build a business schedule that can be integrated with their parenting duties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;concept&quot;&gt;Concept&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fusion Festival combines all styles of the underground electronic music scene and various other styles, sometimes depending on the attendees who choose to play their own music. It is described as a space people go to free their minds from their everyday lives, jobs, studies and other responsibilities. It is the result of the search for an alternative through music, to the system “people are forced to live in”. People go to the Fusion to experience a different way of socializing and living, where experiencing one another freely, sharing love for music and art connects different scenes and minds. It is a clothing-optional event. Art installations include performance arts, static artworks, sculptures, art cars and various other forms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fusion Festival began in 1997 near the city of Lärz in north-eastern Germany, about 160 km from Berlin and 230 km from Hamburg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;festival-site&quot;&gt;Festival Site&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The location is on the original grass-covered grounds of a disused military airfield (at 53°20′48.11″N 12°44′23.25″E for the 234-hectare area central field) about 4.5 km (2.25 miles) due north of the modern Rechlin-Lärz Airfield facility. The site was first acquired by the German Empire in 1916 as an aviation research and training ground, opening the facility for use by the Luftstreitkräfte in August 1918. After the establishment of the Luftwaffe in 1935, the field served as the Erprobungsstelle Rechlin central military aircraft test facility of the Third Reich through early 1945, and it was captured by the Soviet Red Army on May 2, 1945, for use by the VVS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are grass-covered concrete hangars (actual bunkers) from that time that were used for Soviet fighter aircraft (hence the Cyrillic transliteration of the festival name and various stages, as many Cyrillic inscriptions were still present on the site). The airfield was reopened for civilian use in 1994 and sold to the Müritz Airpark Group in 2010. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fusion_Festival&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-working-from-home</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-working-from-home</guid>
                
                <category>tips</category>
                
                <category>work</category>
                
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Welcome to Millennial!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Millennial is a minimalist Jekyll theme. The purpose of this theme is to provide a simple, clean, content-focused blogging platform for your personal site or blog. Below you can find everything you need to get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;getting-started&quot;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/getting-started&quot;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/a&gt;: getting started with installing Millennial, whether you are completely new to using Jekyll, or simply just migrating to a new Jekyll theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;example-content&quot;&gt;Example Content&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/text-formatting&quot;&gt;Text and Formatting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;questions&quot;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This theme is completely free and open source software. You may use it however you want, as it is distributed under the &lt;a href=&quot;http://choosealicense.com/licenses/mit/&quot;&gt;MIT License&lt;/a&gt;. If you are having any problems, any questions or suggestions, feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=My%20question%20about%20Millennial;via=paululele&quot;&gt;tweet at me&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/lenpaul/Millennial/issues/new&quot;&gt;file a GitHub issue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;more-jekyll&quot;&gt;More Jekyll!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lagrange&quot;&gt;Lagrange&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lagrange is a minimalist Jekyll blog theme that I built from scratch. The purpose of this theme is to provide a simple, clean, content-focused blogging platform for your personal site or blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/Lagrange/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the demo&lt;/a&gt;, where you’ll also find instructions on &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/Lagrange/journal/getting-started.html&quot;&gt;how to use install&lt;/a&gt; and use the theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;portfolio-jekyll-theme&quot;&gt;Portfolio Jekyll Theme&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a Jekyll theme built using the &lt;a href=&quot;http://devtipsstarterkit.com/&quot;&gt;DevTips Starter Kit&lt;/a&gt; as a foundation for starting, and following closely the amazing tutorial by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T6jKLsxbFg4&amp;amp;list=PL0CB3OvPhDA_STygmp3sDenx3UpdOMk7P&quot;&gt;Travis Neilson over at DevTips&lt;/a&gt;. The purpose of this theme is to provide a clean and simple website for your portfolio. Emphasis is placed on your projects, which are shown front and center on the home page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything that you will ever need to know about this Jekyll theme is included in &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LeNPaul/portfolio-jekyll-theme&quot;&gt;the repository&lt;/a&gt;, which you can also find in &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/portfolio-jekyll-theme/&quot;&gt;the demo site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jekyll-starter-kit&quot;&gt;Jekyll Starter Kit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Jekyll Starter Kit is a simple framework for starting your own Jekyll project using all of the best practices that I learned from building my other Jekyll themes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LeNPaul/jekyll-starter-kit&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;, where you’ll also find instructions on how to use install and use the theme.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-millennial</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-millennial</guid>
                
                <category>documentation</category>
                
                <category>sample</category>
                
                
                <category>documentation</category>
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Getting Started</title>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;millennial&quot;&gt;Millennial&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millennial is a minimalist Jekyll theme for running a simple, clean, content-focused publishing platform for your publication site or blog through &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;, or on your own server. Everything that you will ever need to know about this Jekyll theme is included in the README below, which you can also find in &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/Millennial/&quot;&gt;the demo site&lt;/a&gt;. For a guide on how to deploy a Jekyll site using GitHub Pages, please check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://paulle.ca/jekyll-tutorials/deploy-jekyll-site-github-pages&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like my work then please consider supporting me with &lt;a href=&quot;https://ko-fi.com/paulle&quot;&gt;Ko-fi&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/8409329/32801138-33a72030-c94a-11e7-8a62-6184e6df5a8f.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;Millennial Demo Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;notable-features&quot;&gt;Notable features&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Compatible with GitHub Pages.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Support for Jekyll’s built-in Sass/SCSS preprocessor and data files for making customizing easier.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/analytics/&quot;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt; support.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Commenting support powered by &lt;a href=&quot;https://disqus.com/&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Optimized for search engines.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;LaTeX support through &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mathjax.org/&quot;&gt;MathJax&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;table-of-contents&quot;&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#what-is-jekyll&quot;&gt;What is Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#never-used-jekyll-before&quot;&gt;Never Used Jeykll Before?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#installation&quot;&gt;Installation&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#github-pages-installation&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages Installation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#local-installation&quot;&gt;Local Installation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#directory-structure&quot;&gt;Directory Structure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#starting-from-scratch&quot;&gt;Starting From Scratch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#configuration&quot;&gt;Configuration&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#sample-posts&quot;&gt;Sample Posts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#site-variables&quot;&gt;Site Variables&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#adding-menu-pages&quot;&gt;Adding Menu Pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#posts&quot;&gt;Posts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#layouts&quot;&gt;Layouts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#yaml-front-block-matter&quot;&gt;YAML Front Block Matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#features&quot;&gt;Features&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#design-considerations&quot;&gt;Design Considerations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#disqus&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#google-analytics&quot;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#rss-feeds&quot;&gt;RSS Feeds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#social-media-icons&quot;&gt;Social Media Icons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#mathjax&quot;&gt;MathJax&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#syntax-highlighting&quot;&gt;Syntax Highlighting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#markdown&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#everything-else&quot;&gt;Everything Else&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Contributing&quot;&gt;Contributing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#questions&quot;&gt;Questions?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#license&quot;&gt;License&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millennial is a Jekyll theme that was built to be 100% compatible with &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;. If you are unfamiliar with GitHub Pages, you can check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/categories/github-pages-basics/&quot;&gt;their documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information. &lt;a href=&quot;http://jmcglone.com/guides/github-pages/&quot;&gt;Jonathan McGlone’s guide&lt;/a&gt; on creating and hosting a personal site on GitHub is also a good resource.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-jekyll&quot;&gt;What is Jekyll?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog-aware, static site generator for personal, project, or organization sites. Basically, Jekyll takes your page content along with template files and produces a complete website. For more information, visit the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home/&quot;&gt;official Jekyll site&lt;/a&gt; for their documentation. Codecademy also offers a great course on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codecademy.com/learn/deploy-a-website&quot;&gt;how to deploy a Jekyll site&lt;/a&gt; for complete beginners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;never-used-jekyll-before&quot;&gt;Never Used Jekyll Before?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beauty of hosting your website on GitHub is that you don’t have to actually have Jekyll installed on your computer. Everything can be done through the GitHub code editor, with minimal knowledge of how to use Jekyll or the command line. All you have to do is add your posts to the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory and edit the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file to change the site settings. With some rudimentary knowledge of HTML and CSS, you can even modify the site to your liking. This can all be done through the GitHub code editor, which acts like a content management system (CMS).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;installation&quot;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;github-pages-installation&quot;&gt;GitHub Pages Installation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start using Jekyll right away with GitHub Pages, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LeNPaul/Millennial/fork&quot;&gt;fork the Millennial repository on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;. From there, you can rename your repository to ‘USERNAME.github.io’, where ‘USERNAME’ is your GitHub username, and edit the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;settings.yml&lt;/code&gt; file in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data&lt;/code&gt; folder to your liking. Ensure that you have a branch named &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt;. Your website should be ready immediately at ‘http://USERNAME.github.io’. Note: if you are hosting several sites under the same GitHub username, then you will have to use &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/articles/user-organization-and-project-pages/&quot;&gt;Project Pages instead of User Pages&lt;/a&gt; - just change the repository name to something other than ‘http://USERNAME.github.io’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head over to the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory to view all the posts that are currently on the website, and to see examples of what post files generally look like. You can simply just duplicate the template post and start adding your own content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;local-installation&quot;&gt;Local Installation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a full local installation of Millennial, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LeNPaul/Millennial/archive/gh-pages.zip&quot;&gt;download your own copy of Millennial&lt;/a&gt; and unzip it into it’s own directory. From there, open up your favorite command line tool, enter &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle install&lt;/code&gt;, and then enter &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;. Your site should be up and running locally at &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;directory-structure&quot;&gt;Directory Structure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are familiar with Jekyll, then the Millennial directory structure shouldn’t be too difficult to navigate. The following some highlights of the differences you might notice between the default directory structure. More information on what these folders and files do can be found in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/structure/&quot;&gt;Jekyll documentation site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Millennial/
├── _data                      &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Data files&lt;/span&gt;
|  └── settings.yml            &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Theme settings and custom text&lt;/span&gt;
├── _includes                  &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Theme includes&lt;/span&gt;
├── _layouts                   &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Theme layouts (see below for details)&lt;/span&gt;
├── _posts                     &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Where all your posts will go&lt;/span&gt;
├── assets                     &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Style sheets and images are found here&lt;/span&gt;
|  ├── css                     &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Style sheets go here&lt;/span&gt;
|  |  └── _sass                &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Folder containing SCSS files&lt;/span&gt;
|  |  └── main.scss            &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Main SCSS file&lt;/span&gt;
|  |  └── syntax.css           &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Style sheet for code syntax highlighting&lt;/span&gt;
|  └── img                     &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Images go here&lt;/span&gt;
├── pages                      &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Category pages&lt;/span&gt;
├── _config.yml                &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Site build settings&lt;/span&gt;
├── Gemfile                    &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Ruby Gemfile for managing Jekyll plugins&lt;/span&gt;
├── index.md                   &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Home page&lt;/span&gt;
├── LICENSE.md                 &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# License for this theme&lt;/span&gt;
├── README.md                  &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Includes all of the documentation for this theme&lt;/span&gt;
└── rss-feed.xml               &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;# Generates RSS 2.0 file which Jekyll points to&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;starting-from-scratch&quot;&gt;Starting From Scratch&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To completely start from scratch, simply delete all the files in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;assets/img&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;pages&lt;/code&gt; folder, and add your own content. You may also replace the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;README.md&lt;/code&gt; file with your own README. Everything in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data&lt;/code&gt; folder and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file can be edited to suit your needs. You may also change the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;favicon.ico&lt;/code&gt; file to your own favicon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;configuration&quot;&gt;Configuration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sample-posts&quot;&gt;Sample Posts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Visit the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/Millennial/&quot;&gt;the demo site&lt;/a&gt; to find sample posts that show what different types of text formatting look like. You can find these posts in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; folder, which show what the best practices for setting up your own site are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;site-variables&quot;&gt;Site Variables&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To change site build settings, edit the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file found in the root of your repository, which you can tweak however you like. More information on configuration settings and plugins can be found on &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/configuration/&quot;&gt;the Jekyll documentation site&lt;/a&gt;. This is also where you will be able to customize the title, description, and the author/owner of your site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are hosting your site on GitHub Pages, then committing a change to the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file will force a rebuild of your site with Jekyll. Any changes made should be viewable soon after. If you are hosting your site locally, then you must run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt; again for the changes to take place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;settings.yml&lt;/code&gt; file found in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data&lt;/code&gt; folder, you will be able to customize your site settings, such as setting Disqus comments, Google Analytics, what shows up in your menu, and social media information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;adding-menu-pages&quot;&gt;Adding Menu Pages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The menu pages are found in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;menu&lt;/code&gt; folder in the root directory, and can be added to your menu in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;settings.yml&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;posts&quot;&gt;Posts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will find example posts in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit any post and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention of &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.md&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at any sample post to get an idea about how it works. If you already have a website built with Jekyll, simply copy over your posts to migrate to Millennial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;layouts&quot;&gt;Layouts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two main layout options that are included with Millennial: post and page. Layouts are specified through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/frontmatter/&quot;&gt;YAML front block matter&lt;/a&gt;. Any file that contains a YAML front block matter will be processed by Jekyll. For example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;---
layout: post
title: &quot;Example Post&quot;
---
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Examples of what posts looks like can be found in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory, which includes this post you are reading right now. Posts are the basic blog post layout, which includes a header image, post content, author name, date published, social media sharing links, and related posts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pages are essentially the post layout without any of the extra features of the posts layout. An example of what pages look like can be found at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/Millennial/pages/documentation.html&quot;&gt;documentation page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the two main layout options above, there are also custom layouts that have been created for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/Millennial/&quot;&gt;home page&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lenpaul.github.io/Millennial/pages/contact.html&quot;&gt;contacts page&lt;/a&gt;. These are simply just page layouts with some &lt;a href=&quot;https://shopify.github.io/liquid/&quot;&gt;Liquid template code&lt;/a&gt;. Check out the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;index.html&lt;/code&gt; file in the root directory for what the code looks like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;yaml-front-block-matter&quot;&gt;YAML Front Block Matter&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The recommended YAML front block is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;---
layout:
title:
author:
categories:
tags: []
image:
---
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;layout&lt;/code&gt; specifies which layout to use, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;title&lt;/code&gt; is the page or post title, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;categories&lt;/code&gt; can be used to better organize your posts, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;tags&lt;/code&gt; are used when generating related posts based on the topic of the post, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;image&lt;/code&gt; specifies which images to use. Have a look at some posts in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory to see how these variables are set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;features&quot;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;design-considerations&quot;&gt;Design Considerations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millennial was designed to be a minimalist theme in order for the focus to remain on your content. For example, links are signified mainly through an underline text-decoration, in order to maximize the perceived affordance of clickability (I originally just wanted to make the links a darker shade of grey).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;disqus&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millennial supports comments at the end of posts through &lt;a href=&quot;https://disqus.com/&quot;&gt;Disqus&lt;/a&gt;. In order to activate Disqus commenting, set &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;disqus.comments&lt;/code&gt; to true in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data/settings.yml&lt;/code&gt; file. If you do not have a Disqus account already, you will have to set one up, and create a profile for your website. You will be given a &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;disqus_shortname&lt;/code&gt; that will be used to generate the appropriate comments sections for your site. More information on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.perfectlyrandom.org/2014/06/29/adding-disqus-to-your-jekyll-powered-github-pages/&quot;&gt;how to set up Disqus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;google-analytics&quot;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is possible to track your site statistics through &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/analytics/&quot;&gt;Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;. Similar to Disqus, you will have to create an account for Google Analytics, and enter the correct Google ID for your site under &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;google-ID&lt;/code&gt; in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;settings.yml&lt;/code&gt; file. More information on &lt;a href=&quot;https://michaelsoolee.com/google-analytics-jekyll/&quot;&gt;how to set up Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;rss-feeds&quot;&gt;RSS Feeds&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Atom is supported by default through &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll-feed&quot;&gt;jekyll-feed&lt;/a&gt;. With jekyll-feed, you can set configuration variables such as ‘title’, ‘description’, and ‘author’, in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSS 2.0 is also supported through &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rssboard.org/rss-autodiscovery&quot;&gt;RSS auto-discovery&lt;/a&gt;. The &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;rss-feed.xml&lt;/code&gt; file (based on the template found at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/snaptortoise/jekyll-rss-feeds&quot;&gt;jekyll-rss-feeds&lt;/a&gt;) that the feed path points to when using RSS 2.0 is automatically generated based on the appropriate configuration variables found in &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data/settings.yml&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To use RSS 2.0, ensure the following is done:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Uncomment the last two lines in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data/settings.yml&lt;/code&gt;, under ‘social’, comment out the rss-square that points to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;feed.xml&lt;/code&gt;, and uncomment the rss-square that points to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;rss-feed.xml&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_includes/head.html&lt;/code&gt;, comment out &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;link type=&quot;application/atom+xml&quot; rel=&quot;alternate&quot; href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/feed.xml&quot; title=&quot;Millennial&quot; /&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and uncomment the line under the RSS 2.0 comment.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;social-media-icons&quot;&gt;Social Media Icons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All social media icons are courtesy of &lt;a href=&quot;http://fontawesome.io/&quot;&gt;Font Awesome&lt;/a&gt;. You can change which icons appear, as well as the account that they link to, in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;settings.yml&lt;/code&gt; file in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_data&lt;/code&gt; folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;mathjax&quot;&gt;MathJax&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millennial comes out of the box with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mathjax.org/&quot;&gt;MathJax&lt;/a&gt;, which allows you to display mathematical equations in your posts through the use of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.andy-roberts.net/writing/latex/mathematics_1&quot;&gt;LaTeX&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;syntax-highlighting&quot;&gt;Syntax Highlighting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millennial provides syntax highlighting through &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/articles/creating-and-highlighting-code-blocks/&quot;&gt;fenced code blocks&lt;/a&gt;. Syntax highlighting allows you to display source code in different colors and fonts depending on what programming language is being displayed. You can find the full list of supported programming languages &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jneen/rouge/wiki/List-of-supported-languages-and-lexers&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Another option is to embed your code through &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.support.wordpress.com/gist/&quot;&gt;Gist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;markdown&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, Jekyll offers support for GitHub Flavored Markdown, which allows you to format your posts using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://guides.github.com/features/mastering-markdown/&quot;&gt;Markdown syntax&lt;/a&gt;. Examples of these text formatting features can be seen below. You can find this post in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory as well as the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;README.md&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;everything-else&quot;&gt;Everything Else&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contributing&quot;&gt;Contributing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to make a feature request, or report a bug or typo in the documentation, then please &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LeNPaul/Millennial/issues/new&quot;&gt;submit a GitHub issue&lt;/a&gt;. If you would like to make a contribution, then feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/articles/about-pull-requests/&quot;&gt;submit a pull request&lt;/a&gt; - as a bonus, I will credit all contributors below! If this is your first pull request, it may be helpful to read up on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://guides.github.com/introduction/flow/&quot;&gt;GitHub Flow&lt;/a&gt; first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Millennial has been designed as a base for users to customize and fit to their own unique needs. Please keep this in mind when requesting features and/or submitting pull requests. Some examples of changes that I would love to see are things that would make the site easier to use, or better ways of doing things. Please avoid changes that do not benefit the majority of users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;questions&quot;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This theme is completely free and open source software. You may use it however you want, as it is distributed under the &lt;a href=&quot;http://choosealicense.com/licenses/mit/&quot;&gt;MIT License&lt;/a&gt;. If you are having any problems, any questions or suggestions, feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=My%question%about%Millennial%is:%&amp;amp;via=paululele&quot;&gt;tweet at me&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/lenpaul/Millennial/issues/new&quot;&gt;file a GitHub issue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;credits&quot;&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;creator&quot;&gt;Creator&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;paul-le&quot;&gt;Paul Le&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://lenpaul.com&quot;&gt;www.lenpaul.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/paululele&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LeNPaul&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;contributors&quot;&gt;Contributors&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/b-morawiec&quot;&gt;b-morawiec&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JainVikas&quot;&gt;JainVikas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mschaeffner&quot;&gt;mschaeffner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/cfe316&quot;&gt;cfe316&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/JeremyGonzales&quot;&gt;JeremyGonzales&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;icons--demo-images&quot;&gt;Icons + Demo Images&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://deathtothestockphoto.com/&quot;&gt;Death to Stock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://fontawesome.io/&quot;&gt;Font Awesome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;other&quot;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freecodecamp.org&quot;&gt;Free Code Camp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.khanacademy.org/&quot;&gt;Khan Academy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;license&quot;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open sourced under the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/LeNPaul/Millennial/blob/gh-pages/LICENSE.md&quot;&gt;MIT license&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/getting-started</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/getting-started</guid>
                
                <category>documentation</category>
                
                <category>sample</category>
                
                
                <category>documentation</category>
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Text Formatting</title>
                <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;markdown-support&quot;&gt;Markdown Support&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, Jekyll offers support for GitHub Flavored Markdown, which allows you to format your posts using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://guides.github.com/features/mastering-markdown/&quot;&gt;Markdown syntax&lt;/a&gt;. Examples of these text formatting features can be seen below. You can find this post in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;basic-formatting&quot;&gt;Basic Formatting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Markdown, it is possible to emphasize words by making them &lt;em&gt;italicized&lt;/em&gt;, using &lt;em&gt;astericks&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;underscores&lt;/em&gt;, or making them &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;, using &lt;strong&gt;double astericks&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;double underscores&lt;/strong&gt;. Of course, you can combine those two formats, with both &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bold and italicized&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; text, using any combination of the above syntax. You can also add a strikethrough to text using a &lt;del&gt;double tilde&lt;/del&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;paragraphs&quot;&gt;Paragraphs&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what a paragraph looks like. For the purpose of demonstration, the rest of this paragraph and the next paragraph after will mean absolutely nothing. Proin eget nibh a massa vestibulum pretium. Suspendisse eu nisl a ante aliquet bibendum quis a nunc. Praesent varius interdum vehicula. Aenean risus libero, placerat at vestibulum eget, ultricies eu enim. Praesent nulla tortor, malesuada adipiscing adipiscing sollicitudin, adipiscing eget est. Praesent nulla tortor, malesuada adipiscing adipiscing sollicitudin, adipiscing eget est.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proin eget nibh a massa vestibulum pretium. Suspendisse eu nisl a ante aliquet bibendum quis a nunc. Mauris lobortis nulla et felis ullamcorper bibendum. Phasellus et hendrerit mauris. Proin eget nibh a massa vestibulum pretium. Suspendisse eu nisl a ante aliquet bibendum quis a nunc. Praesent varius interdum vehicula. Aenean risus libero, placerat at vestibulum eget, ultricies eu enim. Praesent nulla tortor, malesuada adipiscing adipiscing sollicitudin, adipiscing eget est.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;headings&quot;&gt;Headings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes it is useful to have different levels of headings to structure your documents. Start lines with &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;#&lt;/code&gt; to create headings. Multiple &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;##&lt;/code&gt; in a row denote smaller heading size. The following demonstrate the full range of heading sizes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;heading-one-h1&quot;&gt;Heading One (h1)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading-two-h2&quot;&gt;Heading Two (h2)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;heading-three-h3&quot;&gt;Heading Three (h3)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;heading-four-h4&quot;&gt;Heading Four (h4)&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;heading-five-h5&quot;&gt;Heading Five (h5)&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;heading-six-h6&quot;&gt;Heading Six (h6)&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;links&quot;&gt;Links&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can create an inline link by wrapping link text in square brackets &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;[ ]&lt;/code&gt;, and then wrapping the URL in parentheses &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;( )&lt;/code&gt;. For example, it is very easy to &lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com&quot;&gt;link to Google!&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blockquotes are useful for denoting quotes, or highlighting a large block of text. Single line blockquote:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This quote will change your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multi line blockquote with a cite reference:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;People think focus means saying yes to the thing you’ve got to focus on. But that’s not what it means at all. It means saying no to the hundred other good ideas that there are. You have to pick carefully. I’m actually as proud of the things we haven’t done as the things I have done. Innovation is saying no to 1,000 things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;code-and-syntax-highlighting&quot;&gt;Code and Syntax Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code blocks are part of the Markdown spec, but syntax highlighting isn’t. However, many renderers - like GitHub or most Jekyll themes - support syntax highlighting. Which languages are supported and how those language names should be written will vary from renderer to renderer. You can find the full list of supported programming languages &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jneen/rouge/wiki/List-of-supported-languages-and-lexers&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Also, it is possible to do &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;inline code blocks&lt;/code&gt;, by wrapping the text in ` ` ` quotations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;No language indicated, so no syntax highlighting.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-ruby highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Tom&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &apos;Hi, Tom&apos; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Example can be run directly in your JavaScript console&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Create a function that takes two arguments and returns the sum of those arguments&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nc&quot;&gt;Function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dl&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dl&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;dl&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dl&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;dl&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;return a + b&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dl&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Call the function&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// &amp;gt; 8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another option is to embed your code through &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.support.wordpress.com/gist/&quot;&gt;Gist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;unordered-and-numbered-lists&quot;&gt;Unordered and Numbered Lists&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can make an unordered and nested list by preceding one or more lines of text with &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;-&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;*&lt;/code&gt;, or &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;+&lt;/code&gt;, and indenting sublists. The following lists show the full range of possible list formats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item one
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item one
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item one&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Numbered lists are made by using numbers instead of bullet points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item one
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item one
        &lt;ol&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item one&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ol&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mathjax-example&quot;&gt;MathJax Example&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schr%C3%B6dinger_equation&quot;&gt;Schrödinger equation&lt;/a&gt; is a partial differential equation that describes how the quantum state of a quantum system changes with time:&lt;/p&gt;

\[i\hbar\frac{\partial}{\partial t} \Psi(\mathbf{r},t) = \left [ \frac{-\hbar^2}{2\mu}\nabla^2 + V(\mathbf{r},t)\right ] \Psi(\mathbf{r},t)\]

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joseph-Louis_Lagrange&quot;&gt;Joseph-Louis Lagrange&lt;/a&gt; was an Italian mathematician and astronomer who was responsible for the formulation of Lagrangian mechanics, which is a reformulation of Newtonian mechanics.&lt;/p&gt;

\[\frac{\mathrm{d}}{\mathrm{d}t} \left ( \frac {\partial  L}{\partial \dot{q}_j} \right ) =  \frac {\partial L}{\partial q_j}\]

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Title 1&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Title 2&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Title 3&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Title 4&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;lorem&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;lorem ipsum dolor sit&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;embedding&quot;&gt;Embedding&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plenty of social media sites offer the option of embedding certain parts of their site on your own site, such as YouTube and Twitter:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mthtn1X4eUY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;twitter-grid&quot; data-partner=&quot;tweetdeck&quot; href=&quot;https://twitter.com/paululele/timelines/755079130027352064&quot;&gt;New Collection&lt;/a&gt; &lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;inline-html-elements&quot;&gt;Inline HTML elements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML defines a long list of available inline tags, which you can mix with Markdown if you like. A complete list of which can be found on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTML/Element&quot;&gt;Mozilla Developer Network&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;useful-resources&quot;&gt;Useful Resources&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More information on Markdown can be found at the following links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/wiki/Markdown-Here-Cheatsheet#code&quot;&gt;Markdown Here Cheatsheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.unexpected-vortices.com/sw/rippledoc/quick-markdown-example.html&quot;&gt;Quick Markdown Example&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/basics&quot;&gt;Markdown Basics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.github.com/gfm/&quot;&gt;GitHub Flavoured Markdown Spec&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/articles/basic-writing-and-formatting-syntax/#lists&quot;&gt;Basic writing and formatting syntax&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/text-formatting</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/text-formatting</guid>
                
                <category>sample</category>
                
                
                <category>sample</category>
                
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>Learning Resources</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The beauty of computer programming is that you do not need to formally go to school to learn how to program. You can learn almost everything that you would need to know online, and for free. The following resources are some that I have used personally, that I highly recommend, for anyone looking to learn more about computer programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;free-code-camp&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.freecodecamp.org/&quot;&gt;Free Code Camp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My personal favourite for learning full stack web development. They offer a great front and back end curriculum that requires you to complete a variety of projects in order to apply the knowledge that you learn during the lessons. As a bonus, at the end of the curriculum you will have a few impressive projects under your belt for your portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;codecademy&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codecademy.com/&quot;&gt;Codecademy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only does Codecademy have many great courses on various web development languages such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codecademy.com/learn/learn-html&quot;&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codecademy.com/learn/learn-css&quot;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codecademy.com/learn/introduction-to-javascript&quot;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;, but they even offer a course on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codecademy.com/learn/deploy-a-website&quot;&gt;how to deploy a Jekyll site&lt;/a&gt;. If you are completely new to Jekyll, I would recommend working through that course as a great start for learning how to deploy your Jekyll site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;khan-academy&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.khanacademy.org/&quot;&gt;Khan Academy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A great resource not only for learning mathematics (what most people probably know Khan Academy for), but also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.khanacademy.org/computing/computer-programming&quot;&gt;computer programming&lt;/a&gt;. What Khan Academy offers that is different from the other two above resources is that it offers courses in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.khanacademy.org/computing/computer-science&quot;&gt;computer science related&lt;/a&gt; topics, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.khanacademy.org/computing/computer-science/algorithms&quot;&gt;algorithms&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.khanacademy.org/computing/computer-science/cryptography&quot;&gt;cryptography&lt;/a&gt;. This is unique in that most online resources mostly focus on the programming side of things.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
                <link>http://localhost:4000/learning-resources</link>
                <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/learning-resources</guid>
                
                <category>documentation</category>
                
                <category>sample</category>
                
                
                <category>resources</category>
                
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>